casinosoviet.com 2010-11-20

# Casino Soviet

| 

Privacy  
  
---  
  
What information do we collect, and why?

  * When you make a deposit, in order to place a wager for real money, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process your request and mail any winnings resulting from wagers placed on any of our gaming services. 

  * When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can run the contest and notify winners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

  * When you participate in a customer survey, we may ask for your name, address, and other personal information. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

  * We monitor player traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and enhance the design of our gaming web sites.

  * We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Will Casino Soviet disclose a player's personal information to other parties?

  * Casino Soviet does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Casino Soviet may provide aggregate statistics about our players, sales, Internet traffic, and related site information to a reputable third-party. However, these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

  * Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from our partners and any promotional communication: 
    1. You can send an email to [support@casinosoviet.com](mailto:support@casinosoviet.com) to opt out of receiving communications

**Amendments to Privacy Statement**

  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. 

**Conclusion**

  * Casino Soviet makes protecting your privacy a top priority. We use the information we collect on the site to facilitate the exchange of wagered funds, and to enhance your overall gaming experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. 

**Contacting Casino Soviet**

  * If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our practices, or your dealings with Casino Soviet, you can contact: [support@casinosoviet.com](mailto:support@casinosoviet.com)
